Hi, it's Mike with UGtastic. I've been on a little bit of a hiatus, not by choice,
but had some things coming up in the real world that kind of put a damper on any kind
of publication and now that things are sorted out, UGtastic is back and I'll be publishing
again. So basically I lost some equipment and thought I lost all the video templates
when I was transferring from my old computer to no computer for a little while when I
was changing jobs and just between sick kids and all kinds of other fun stuff and cost
kidding, kind of getting out of control. I've reeled everything back in. I've got a new
employer now, UpCity.com. We do SEO services, basically guidance for small businesses that
are looking to get into the SEO and don't have the money or the wherewithal to afford
a very expensive SEO consultant. So it's exciting to be able to work on something where I'll
be able to help people save money but increase their own online presence through improved
SEO practices. So I've got a new microphone to replace the old one. I'm changing up the
way I'm going to be recording videos before I was recording directly from the computer
itself from my MacBook Pro. Now I'm going to be recording using an iPad mini hooked
up to a harness and that's going to be delivered. Well I have the iPad mini here so it's right
there but the harness is coming in the next, well tomorrow and I'll be hooking that up
and syncing that up back to my new MacBook Pro where I'll be doing the editing. I'm
very excited, it's a brand new Mavericks space computer. So I've recovered all of my old
iMovie templates so I'll be able to start publishing the Web Vision series again. A
couple months ago now I went to the Web Visions 2013 in Chicago and did a number of interviews
but only was able to publish a few before things kind of got hectic and I couldn't
do the editing any longer. So going to be resuming that series and very exciting news
is next week I'm going to be at SCNA, Software Craftsmanship North America Conference. I'm
going to be a media sponsor. UGtastic is now an official media sponsor so if you go
to the Software Craftsmanship North America Conference website and go to the sponsors
page you'll be able to see that UGtastic is now officially a sponsor of SCNA which
is particularly exciting for me because SCNA is where UGtastic was born. SCNA 2011 was
the place I launched the idea and the concept and actually launched my first interviews
for UGtastic. So it's very exciting to go from being at the conference and launching
the idea of UGtastic to now coming back again third year in a row and being an official
part of the conference as a media sponsor. So looking forward to that, looking forward
to launching more interviews, getting those user group lists up and running and getting
some of those people that have submitted their user groups in the UK, the Brighton
PHP group and another group that I'm just trying to blank on right now but they're going
to be up and posted on the website as soon as I'm able. So thank you again for holding
out and your patience and I'm really looking forward to getting back into the saddle with
UGtastic again.